Don't leave me alone
Trembling in the dark night
Don't leave me alone Don't leave me…
SHENG 2026 CONCERT
"DON'T LEAVE ME ALONE" HITS GLOBAL SUCCESS
I'm used to having you around
I really can't lose you
If you still love me
Can you hold me tight again?
Thank you.
You're like my family.
Without you,
I wouldn't be here.
THE FIXERS
NIGHT AND DAY
Attorney Chao Ming-cheng
dropped a bombshell earlier today
at the Ming Young Party's fundraiser,
releasing a video clip of his son
being framed by mobsters.
I'm happy you're here.
Dad hates it when I come.
Otherwise, I'd go to
all these shallow social events.
-Make sure he stays out of trouble.
-Um, sure.
Fortune, I told you
you can't play with that one.
Find another one. Go.
Are you okay? Did you get hurt?
-You've been training.
-Just talent with the ball.
Two years' practice can't match
your brother's three months of training.
Use two hands on your backhand.
You could have won earlier.
Dragging out a win will still count
as a loss. Hear what I'm saying?
You did a good job.
Very good.
Keep it up.
Hmm.
-Sir.
-Ah, hello.
Tristan, come with me.
Come say hi to the speaker.
-Hello, sir.
-Hello there.
-This is Tristan.
-Ah.
You should have said that you were here.
You were all so busy.
What would we be busy with?
Howie, time for breakfast.
Brooding heartthrob Sheng
wooed fans last night…
So, where did you go last night?
When you used to finish a big job,
you'd come home, and you'd channel surf.
Tell me if you're in trouble.
What do you mean by trouble?
My biggest trouble's standing over there.
You can say that again.
Who could that be this early?
Uh, and you are?
Does Felix Chiang live here?
Yeah.
Felix.
-Yeah?
-It's for you.
Sheng's new album has been released…
-I am from Ching He Temple.
-Ching He?
I'd like you to come with me.
We'd like to talk to you at Ching He.
Uh, I didn't donate a lot last year.
But thank you for the recognition.
Uh, sure.
Howie, finish what you're doing.
Get off to school now.
Oh, big shot now, are you?
You've gone from cop car to luxury car.
Milky, I'm busy now.
I'll make tea another day, huh?
You kidding me?
Fuck tea. You're dead
unless you pay me what you owe.
Milky.
Can I ask if you'd like to come with us
to Ching He for tea?
The boss is talking. Don't cut in.
Quiet!
Sir, I'm sorry.
The young ones, you know?
Let me open the door for you.
Sir.
Don't grovel, all right?
There's a good boy.
Who are those people?
The boss once told me
that if I ever run into Ching He's people,
then to stay far away.
Our friend's gonna wind up
swamp eel noodles.
Damn it.
Sir.
Hey.
The chairman of Ching He, Thackery Huang.
Thank you for your help.
Oh, don't worry.
I promise I'll keep last night a secret.
-Ah.
-My mouth's like my liver.
They're both made of steel.
-Do you remember Sir Hong?
-I don't recall where I slept last night.
Do you recall San He?
You protected someone for them,
and they were killed.
Do you recall that? Do you?
Uh…
Ten years ago, Black Bull,
the leader of Chamber Thirteen.
You know who took him out?
It was me.
Sir, I don't doubt what you're saying.
But I don't know this person Black Bull.
I think you must be mistaken.
When you and Chen Liang-chi
were fighting for control of San He…
…nobody could rival you,
you in particular.
You never killed.
You'd only destroy their kneecaps.
Sir,
I was just trying to make a living.
Hmm. It's been over a decade.
Your aim is still as sharp as ever.
Would you consider
doing work for us here?
It's not possible.
I'm not as sharp as I once was.
And this hand…
Uh, long story short,
I can't really work for you.
From what I hear,
you're in need of some help lately.
If you decide to work for us,
you'll have enough money.
Well, that's not really necessary.
I just want my family safe
and you not to visit the house.
May our paths never cross again,
and may we each enjoy our own freedoms.
See you, bye. Bye.
I… wonder
if there are other candidates around.
Give him some time.
He'll return to Ching He.
Fortune.
Wait. Go.
That's all.
Remember what the vet said to you.
Peace.
This is it.
The super popular idol Sheng
has done it again.
He's breaking all sales records
with the release of his new album.
SHENG ANNOUNCES TAIPEI ARENA CONCERT
All right. Sit.
Good dog. Wait here.
See you tonight.
Welcome.
The bread's just fresh out of the oven.
Give me a three-in-one combo, sir.
One three-in-one.
Pineapple, scallion, pork floss.
-Make it hot.
-Okay.
Hey. Feeling better?
Yeah, I'm all fine now.
It was nothing.
I've survived worse than that.
Oh, tough guy, are you?
Three-in-one combo, ready to go.
Your wife ask any questions?
I saw a babe, got distracted and crashed.
She believed that, did she?
Mm.
Thank you.
Here.
Mm. You come straight home after. Okay?
What are you laughing at?
We need dressing. We're out.
Okay.
-Here.
-What's this?
It's for your son.
He could have gotten it from you just now.
It means more if it's from his dad.
Hey. Has the chairman said
who's replacing me?
I'm sure he'll agree
that I should work on my own.
You should know he'd never do that.
He'd never agree to anything
that violates the rules.
CHING HE TEMPLE: EIGHT O'CLOCK TONIGHT
Chen Chia-yun.
Food's here.
Chen Chia-yun?
Aren't you sick of watching this?
Don't scare me like that.
What happened to you?
Who hurt you?
-Rabid dog.
-A dog? Really?
I got you a 70/30.
Oh! My ticket!
Aw! Sheng's face is dirty now,
and it's all wet.
Why'd you do that?
Hey.
Oh.
This ticket, it's making you stressed.
It's a concert I've been waiting ages for,
all right?
-You're going with a guy?
-Why say that?
You're going with a boyfriend, aren't you?
-I'm not.
-"I'm not. I'm not."
Hey, this was in the mail.
Looks important, huh?
What is it?
The US exam board
sent an acceptance letter!
Oh yeah!
The temple towers loom tall.
Like father, like daughter.
-You're in luck.
-I just thought I'd try it
I don't have to do it.
Don't worry about money. That's my part.
I can make it after I graduate.
Your father and I never achieved much,
but luckily you got your mom's brains.
You get a chance, you go for it.
I'll sort out money.
Hello?
Hello there.
I'm calling from Hsing Tai Bank.
-Are you Mr. Chiang?
-Yes, I am.
This is a courtesy call to remind you
that your loan payment for the month
hasn't been paid.
-Eat something.
-It's already overdue.
Please handle it as soon as possible
to avoid
your credit rating being affected.
Okay.
Okay, I understand.
Thank you. Thank you.
Parkinson's disease?
That makes no sense.
I don't know if I've had
a serious illness ever.
I've only hurt my right hand.
Your situation is relatively uncommon.
You have concurrent action tremors
apart from what you're getting
in your hand.
Uh, how is this treated?
Will my left hand go the same way?
The disease is caused by the degeneration
of substantia nigra cells in the brain.
-Dopamine secretion will--
-Hey, hey, Doctor, clearer, clearer.
It's incurable,
if you want to hear it clearer.
However, active treatment
and medication can delay its progression.
So, after that,
then what then?
Some patients experience disability
or dementia in the final stages.
But the rate of progression can vary.
Some patients go from the initial stage
to final stage in three months,
but, uh, some patients do better
and might have ten years or more.
Sweetheart,
after Howie finishes his exams,
let's go on an overseas holiday.
I've never taken you guys abroad.
The chairman says that you can go in now.
Okay.
You should know
I won't do anything unethical.
You don't need to worry.
We're not killers or even criminals.
TAI SUI HALL
We just help people take care of problems.
This type of fish is called a cleaner.
They like to hide in murky water.
They have no natural predators
and are extremely resilient.
But humans don't like them.
They think they're dirty and smelly.
But without them, the water would be
too polluted for anything to survive in.
Ching He's fixers
are just like this type of fish.
Business identities, politicians,
whichever side of the law,
when they have a situation
they can't handle personally,
they'll hire us
to discreetly clean up the mess for them.
We try to stay above
both sides of the law.
We never play favorites.
Here, you won't go by your name.
You'll have a code name.
Oh? Well, that's easy.
See, people call me Swamp Eel.
CHING HE
We choose all code names for fixers
from the Thousand Character Classic.
So what's mine?
What's this about?
What? You again?
Let me tell you, you're still on my radar.
This is Fixer Gold.
And from now on, he's your partner.
-You're joking.
-What?
Only Fixer Shadow tolerated your temper.
No other fixer is willing
to work with you.
And now his kneecap is injured.
It will take at least six months
for him to recover.
I can do it unaided.
Without a partner.
-Especially not that dinosaur over there.
-You condescending fuck.
Fixers work in twos.
That's our rule.
And I've decided,
until Fixer Shadow returns,
that you two are partners.
CHING HE
FELIX CHIANG, AGE 55, NICKNAME: SWAMP EEL
Ching He has three rules.
Fixers must always abide by them.
-Sir Hong.
-All right.
Whether dead or alive,
first, fixers must never reveal
any secrets of Ching He.
Second, fixers must obey orders.
Unless expressly asked to by Ching He,
fixers must never abandon their mission
before completion.
Third, fixers must not reveal
their identity ever,
nor alter their mission objectives
due to personal beliefs.
Okay, then what happens
if a fixer is defiant?
One word.
Death.
Oh.
If you're afraid, you can go.
I'm not afraid.
This game has rules we have to obey.
Don't you know that?
Our mission this time is to destroy
the client's daughter's sex tape.
Who is the client?
A prosecutor
from the district prosecutor's office,
Yen Wen-chieh.
Ms. Yen's daughter and the singer Sheng
filmed a sex video.
They were dating at the time.
Now they've broken up.
Miss Yen's worried
the video will be leaked,
so she's contracted Ching He
to make it disappear.
Use this to communicate from now on.
Uh, I don't know
what name you're calling me.
Fixer Butthole.
Complete this mission first,
then you'll find out.
What? Is this your car too?
Does being a fixer pay that well?
You drive a different car every day.
Hey. I'm your partner.
You can't get rid of me now.
Find an opportunity
to plant this on Sheng.
-Then figure out a way to get his phone.
-And then?
I'll tell you what to do.
Okay, let's drive.
Fuck you! Asswipe!
Disloyal son of a bitch. Shit!
Trackers these days are tiny.
Looks like a button cell battery.
How do I get near that Sheng guy?
BOOHOO, MY TICKET GOT DIRTY
Albums. Album.
CHIA-YUN
Uh, is this the way to the backstage area?
-Are you a staff member?
-No, I'm not.
If you're not staff,
you can't go backstage.
You sure?
The show's started. You'll need to hurry.
As you can see, our entryway
was designed to attract wealth.
For fortune, we hired Master Tang to--
Can you cut the crap? Answer the question.
-Where's the elevator?
-This way, please. This way, thank you.
Let me press the button.
So, who lives in this building?
Prominent businesspeople and politicians,
but they're not as handsome--
Are they noisy,
the people above and below?
Oh, no, no, they're not noisy at all.
But I'm not at liberty
to reveal who they are.
I wanna sense the energy
in the living room. Wait over there.
Don't come out till I say.
Oh, you want me to…
-Uh-huh.
-Oh. Oh, then…
OK. Yell out if you need anything.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Watch out, watch out.
Hi.
Can you set up a proxy, Fixer Stealth?
I'm coding 24/7. I'm busy.
Cut the crap.
I used your program to hack the computer,
but there's fuck-all on it.
My guess is
he stored the videos on his phone.
Do you have a way to hack into it?
There's a Trojan already in there.
But… but to delete the videos,
you'll have to get hold of his phone.
Send the surveillance footage
from his messaging app straight to me.
Uh… Oh.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
SHENG, ARTIST'S DRESSING ROOM
Hi. I was told
there's an issue with the air con. Yeah?
That's good.
You're like my family.
Thank you, everyone.
I will definitely return.
I know he shouldn't turn it down.
But after today's performance,
he… he really needs to rest.
That's what the doctor said.
Listen, we need to think long term, okay?
Oh, um…
Oh, he's here. I'll call you later.
Okay, bye.
Hey! Are you okay?
Where'd they put the fans?
Oh, in the, um, exit passageway.
I've got someone standing watch.
Uh… uh, we need to clear out
the dressing room for a minute.
Come on, thank you. Sir.
-Huh?
-We need to clear out the dressing room.
Okay, I'm coming.
I'm sorry.
-That's all right. It's all right.
-Thank you.
Hello. Hi.
-Sheng!
-Wow, look at that.
I'm yours.
Sheng! Sheng, can I have your autograph?
Over here.
Can you write, "To Chia-yun" for me?
Uh, excuse me. Excuse me.
Give me your autograph.
Put it on my chest here.
-Sorry, let's not get too close.
-No, no, I really like him.
-I've bought every album. I like you.
-Stand back.
I like you so much.
Give me your autograph.
Oh, don't be like that.
Give me your autograph!
-That's all. Thank you.
-Bye!
Felix Chiang!
What are you doing here?
-Don't say you stole it!
-No, listen.
You got it wet and then robbed me.
Do you know how much scalpers charged me?
Will you let me explain?
Since when were you a fan?
Uh, never.
Howie has midterms and couldn't come.
-He insisted I come get his autograph.
-Howie?
He's his idol.
Now, can I ask
what did he whisper to you before?
Just now?
-The release!
-Hey.
This Sheng's not a good guy. Hey!
Don't forget
you've got an interview later.
No more.
Prepare me a hotel suite.
Uh, but you said you'd do it.
This is the sec--
No interview.
Mm-hmm. Okay, okay.
Close it.
HI, IT'S SHENG.
THANKS FOR COMING. FREE LATER?
GOT A NEW DROP TODAY
MUST BE NICE TO BE HANDSOME!
WHAT KIND OF FAN IS IT?
FUCK! THE OBSESSIVE TYPE. SUPER FORWARD
WHERE ARE YOU UNWRAPPING IT?
THEY GOT MIRRORS
DON'T END UP IN THE NEWS LIKE DONG
FUCK, THANKS FOR CLEANING UP MY MESS, TAI!
BRING HER OVER FOR A FEW DRINKS NEXT TIME
AFTER YOU'VE HAD YOUR FUN!
Hello, X Hotel. Can I help you?
Book me a room tonight on the top floor.
Say that it's for Louis.
Sorry, all our rooms are booked today,
so I…
Tell Mr. Yao
that it's for Mr. Hsueh's son. Hear me?
Yes, sir.
Ring to confirm.
I gotta go. I got another call.
Hello? Mission accomplished. What's next?
Done it already?
Of course I have. It was child's play.
Well, congratulations.
-You can go home now.
-Huh?
Hey, I worked hard to plant this tracker.
Shouldn't I follow him now?
Who said that it's a tracker?
What else is it?
A regular button cell.
A button cell battery?
Why do we need to plant
a button cell battery on him?
You tell me. You planted it.
Man, I show you respect,
and now this is all I get.
Hey.
Fuck!
-Hey, hello? Chia-yun.
-How dare you call me?
I…
I have a question for you.
That Sheng guy, where is he going next?
Why are you asking me this?
Tell me first, and I'll explain later.
It's urgent. Okay?
He's going to X Hotel.
You're not a stan, are you? Are you?!
How do you know he's going to a hotel?
Did he tell you that?
Hey, are you there as well?
I'm at home already.
The stan group track his itinerary.
But I'm not a stan.
What language is this? I don't understand.
You're not even part of the fandom.
Forget it.
Wait, wait…
LET'S MEET AT X HOTEL, 3105
Oh, Mr. Yao,
French cheese and sparkling water.
-For two. Send it to the room.
-Certainly. Right away.
Sorry about meeting here.
There's always paparazzi at the house.
Getting photographed,
that must be exciting for you.
Do you like the camera?
Ha!
All around mountains and waters combine.
You're not so divine. I found you.
Damn.
Piece of cake.
Can you deliver this to the suite
across the hall? Say it's from Mr. Yao.
Okay.
Room service?
It's compliments of the hotel manager.
Stealth? Get me intel on all the people
Sheng shares videos with.
Including their backgrounds.
Okay, after this, I'm done.
I… I've done too much overtime.
My wife's raising the baby on her own.
The baby bottle sterilizer
broke down yesterday.
Do you know how many bottles…
What a unique necklace.
Don't you think…
doing it at the window
is even more fun?
Bingo.
Now…
have you ever tried
doing it while being filmed?
That's exciting.
Here we are. Back in the elevator.
Who sent you here?
Hand it over.
Hey.
Not the taser.
Catch!
-Run! Run!
-What?
Hand it over now.
You want the phone? Then ask for it.
Why shoot my tires?
I just had them changed, you know.
She actually wanted to destroy the phone.
Turns out her goal was the same as ours.
I'll pass all this on to the chairman.
Do you think
that she's from Yeh Yueh Tong?
It's possible.
But her style's not Yeh Yueh Tong's.
She's not as ruthless.
I understand.
Go and deliver the phone to Ms. Yen.
Felix,
for your first mission,
you've been very resourceful.
Yeah, yeah.
You should know I'm pissed off.
This asshole tried to pass off
a button cell battery as a tracker.
Luckily, I was two steps ahead of him,
and I switched his phone with my phone.
I wanted to see
what you were capable of, old man.
Now, hold on.
I need to buy a new phone now.
Can I get reimbursed?
Of course. It's good to hear
you're working well together.
All right, get going.
Hey, where'd you get that idea?
This jerk…
No money yet, and I need new tires.
I'm going down the toilet here.
Listen, you're paying for those.
Ridiculous.
Ms. Yen, I have a child of my own.
I understand how you feel.
Hey. That Yeh Yueh Tong, who are they?
-It would mean nothing to you.
-You gonna say or not?
Their founder was
excommunicated from Ching He.
After she started up her own organization,
she took a lot of their business.
I can't watch anymore. I can't.
It's not just your daughter's videos.
As long as they're all deleted,
no one will be able to use them again.
There were no backups made.
Once they're deleted, it's over.
Delete them all.
If this sort of thing
happened to my child,
I'd be at a loss too.
Fixers aren't shrinks.
No one cares if you're empathetic.
What? You heartless bastard.
You didn't see that Sheng guy yourself.
From the look of him,
he's a regular cocaine user.
CHIA-YUN
Ah, fuck!
Chen Chia-yun's gonna chew me out.
SHENG'S EXPLICIT VIDEO GOES VIRAL
What? How'd this happen?
Weren't all the videos deleted?
It's not Miss Yen's daughter.
There's another victim.
You're like my family.
Don't leave me alone…
Without you, I wouldn't be here.
DISGUSTING. DROP HIM.
SURELY SHE LURED HIM
I'll definitely come back again.
Don't leave me alone
Hire thugs, investigators, I don't care.
Find that woman for me.
We've got an account number.
And no cops.
You got that?
Yeh Yueh Tong hasn't even made a move yet,
but Ching He's
already knocking on our door.
-Madam Fan.
-Mm.
This should get fun.